acttestpanels.com 2016-06-24

# ACT Test Panels

### Privacy Policy

We respect your right to privacy and will protect it when you visit our website. This page explains how we handle information when you visit and use our site. ACT provides this website as a public service to you — you do not have to provide any personal information in order to enter and browse. The extent and type of information we receive depends on what you do while you are visiting our website.  
ACT does not collect any personal information about you when you visit our website unless you specifically and knowingly choose to provide such information to us. If you choose to provide information to us, we use it only to fill your order or request for information and services.

**Statistical Information Collected and Stored Automatically**

Our website automatically records website usage information that we analyze statistically to track operational problems, to prevent fraud and to improve the effectiveness, security and integrity of the site. This information does not identify you personally and we do not use this information to track or record information about individuals. We will not disclose this information to third parties unless required by law.

**Information That You Voluntarily Provide**

If you voluntarily provide us with personal information, for example by sending an e-mail or by filling out a form and submitting it through our Website, you are indicating voluntary consent for us to use the information you are submitting to respond to your message and to help us provide you with the information and services that you have requested.  On some pages you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials.  The types of personal information collected include:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email
  * Phone number
  * Credit/Debit Card Information

We do not give, sell, or rent any personal information to third parties for any purpose including commercial marketing.

**Security of Personal Information**

We use commercial encryption techniques to protect the transmission and storage of the information you submit to us when you use one of our secure online forms. E-mail that you send to us is not necessarily secure against third-party interception or misdirection. For your own protection, you may wish to communicate sensitive information using a method other than e-mail.

**Access and Maintenance of Personal Information**

You can access all your personal account information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your account from our shop online feature.  To protect your privacy and security we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Links To Other Sites**

Our website contains links to the websites of other public and private organizations that are outside of our control. When you follow a link to another site, you leave the ACT site and your website interactions are no longer protected by our privacy policy.

**Cookies**

Websites may send small pieces of text called cookies along with some of the web pages that you visit. Cookies are typically used on transactional pages as place-holders to retain context and content during individual user sessions, making it easier for you to use the dynamic features of these web pages without having to provide the same information repeatedly as you move from one page to another during your visit.  

**Interaction With Children**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us.  For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13 and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
